hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
jeremia Mike Krakowski we haven't met
yet I help coaches trainers and mentors
scale their businesses to forty thousand
dollars per month and Beyond
and I want to help you get more sales
more leads more clients and more
customers into your coaching and online
course business now in this episode I
want to take you behind the scenes into
a million dollar a month sales funnel
and what it actually takes to do that so
I have a client of mine that we worked
with from 2018 all the way up until uh a
couple months ago this year and now he's
since pivoted and gone into a different
direction with his business and so we're
no longer working with him but we built
his sales funnel to over a million
dollars per month and I'm gonna walk you
through behind the scenes inside how to
do that because really it's a case study
of everything that we learned of what to
do and what not to do here's what not to
do
don't ever map out and plan out your
course or coaching program before you
launch
here's another thing to not to do
don't make all your graphics and your
design and your websites all super
pretty none of that matters
want to know it does matter
is the offer copy that you use a lot of
people don't know what offer copy is so
offer copy is the language
and the words that you use
on a website that people connect with
you with where they they visit the
website
and they see
some kind of a a
problem that they have and a solution
that you offer so with this offer with
Rick Pino
what we did was
it was an offer written towards worship
songwriters
now originally when he launched this we
launched with a program called worship
coach
and it was inspired off of the work that
my mom and I had done together with her
Inner Circle to build a membership of
multiple courses for worshipers and it
was about 27 a month people could join
and this was pretty successful it
actually scaled to forty thousand
dollars per month consistently it
brought in that much revenue there were
thousands of members paying to get new
courses during the pandemic every single
week but that's not what actually scaled
this funnel to a million dollars per
month
here's what actually scaled it was
not having multiple people paying 27 a
month
or paying you know 300 a year it was
having less people
paying more money
and that's where most people miss it is
they think that their profits are going
to come from having lots of little sales
it's actually way easier to sell a five
and ten thousand dollar program to less
people and to ultra qualify those people
and so originally when worship coach
launched
um it was
directed towards
anybody who wanted to learn about
worship whether it be songwriting
playing instruments
growing in Theology and it's pretty cool
it got a lot of great results but it was
like okay that's nice but
why would anybody invest ten thousand
dollars into learning further into that
Niche let me tell you why they would
so we identified
that there was a segment of that market
we niched down further and here's a big
unlock for you is when you discover your
Niche the niche that you use initially
may not always be the niche that you use
forever
it may not always be the niche that
you're going to use
long term
so when we were doing
worship discipleship
we ended up niching down towards worship
songwriters
and those people were actually willing
to spend and invest more money
they were willing to invest not just 27
a month they were willing to invest a
thousand to two thousand to five
thousand dollars to get their music
heard by people and so I want you to
think about that you gotta think in
terms of
the customer life cycle
the client Journey life cycle okay
so when you're coaching
your clients they all start from like
there's a wide net of people right who
may have an interest in what you're
doing but there's a much smaller group
of people
that are willing to invest five ten
even as upward as 20 to 30 thousand
dollars
into what you're doing and
that's the group that you really want to
speak to
and you want to build everything around
that group that's willing to invest the
most with you
don't let your bleeding heart wanting to
help so many people
stop you from actually scaling with
profitable offers you need to have
profitability
in your coaching business in your course
business for it to even be worth your
time and so when we were reaching all of
these people we found that with this
this million dollar funnel
million dollar a month funnel and how do
we get it to a million dollars a month
I'm gonna explain this to you
I'm gonna go start to finish through it
we had identified okay
people
want to
learn how to write better songs
they want to learn how to get their
songs heard
and they want to learn how to grow in
their brand growing their influence and
reach more people
with those songs Beyond just okay I'm
writing songs in my quiet time I love
Jesus and so I'm just writing this music
because it's fun for me rather people
who wanted to make a music career and
wanted to become
somebody who goes on tour with their
songs and it became more of their
identity as a song writer as a worship
leader as somebody who was building a
brand around that
and initially this is something that I
had told Rick
that he needed to do
but he was a little bit hesitant to it
because he was like well I don't really
want to you know teach people how to
make their songs go viral that's not
going to help anybody I want to I want
to teach them how to get closer to God
and I was like okay that's great
but they really want to make their songs
go viral and that's what's going to make
you the most amount of money in this
Niche and so what took it to
a million dollar a month
coaching program
was when we started
like speaking directly to that desire of
get your worship music heard launch your
worship music
get people to listen to your songs
and when we started building offers and
we went and we niched down further to
people who had already written songs but
were struggling to gain traction with
them
those people were much more willing to
invest
five to ten to twenty thousand dollars
in a program to learn how to do that and
so how do you say well twenty thousand
dollars well here's how it actually
worked out is people were able to invest
one to two thousand dollars a month for
a 12-month program okay
and so if somebody's investing a
thousand dollars a month into a 12-month
commitment
and they could save twenty percent off
for paying in full that's a ten thousand
dollar program
and Rick got over
160 people in one month to actually sign
up for that it's like incredible like
okay 160 people
at ten thousand dollars that's a that's
1.6 million dollars
and so that was 160 people that wanted
to be mentored and trained for an entire
year on how to do this and now here's
the really cool part
is we were able to use a tool that I use
in my business called coach financing
which allows people to take out a loan
for the 10 000 or the twelve thousand
dollars and pay it back over time okay
and so people were taking out loans
to be able to join this coaching program
for a year
and get mentored and get that
information what came out of it was
absolutely incredible and so this is
what was inside of that sales funnel is
we had to identify let's go back big
picture here okay we had this whole
group of people
these worshipers these Christians
but we noticed they like they didn't
want to buy anything else that we were
offering it was like
how much further can you go into just
you know grow in your walk with god like
people weren't wanting to buy that
they wanted something more tangible so
we ran what we called an AMA event
an AMA event was where we
had people submit questions and we
surveyed his whole audience and what we
found was
the majority of those people
all wanted to learn how to write better
songs and get their songs heard the ones
who actually joined the AMA event so we
ended up building
a course around songwriting that sold
like crazy quarter of a million dollars
in sales
it was a hundred dollar course
he sold
copies of it
using paid advertising using Facebook
ads and so we were able to build our
our advertising algorithm out
to run Facebook ads to reach people that
wanted this one of the ways that we did
this was we took the audience that was
already connecting with his worship
training
and
we created an ebook offer basically as a
free ebook on how to write better
worship songs
we targeted that out and we got 3 000
people that registered for that free
ebook Okay so go with me here 3 000
people
registered for the free ebook on how to
write better worship songs
and so they've already
just by simply registering have said I
want to learn how to write better
worship songs okay we took that audience
into the algorithm and Facebook and said
okay find US 10 million more people like
those 3 000 that register for this ebook
and so Facebook was able to find us what
it believed was at least 10 million
people that were similar to
who were worship songwriters okay
and then from there
we were able to Market a school of
songwriting and Rick brought together
some of the best worship songwriters on
the planet sold
2500 copies
of that school was a six-week school all
about songwriting and he ran the school
again 1500 people paid for the school
again so we're already at four I think
it was close to four hundred thousand
dollars in Revenue in two months
just by selling schools related to
songwriting
and that's where then things took off
like crazy
we ended up creating an offer
that was a thousand dollars
called songwriters LaunchPad
songwriters Launchpad was specifically
designed for the people who had gone
through those schools those four
thousand people who had gone through
those schools
and wanted to know
how do I actually launch my music out
there how do I actually launch a record
how do I actually get people to listen
to my songs and it was it was an event
that was live and I was a part of this
event and we ended up teaching it
together that some of you who listen to
this podcast may actually have been at
that event
and so that event it was sold for a
thousand dollars and I believe we had
almost 200 people register for it in one
month
so there's another two hundred thousand
dollars right so in less than I think
four months we had brought in six
hundred thousand dollars in Revenue in
this specific niche
and this is where things got crazy this
is how it became a million dollar a
month Revenue stream okay
we ended up saying what if we took that
live event that was a thousand dollars
and we made it a course
and then we bundled a bunch of bonus
content into it and we ran a series of
three day events that were free that
people could register for I think we got
almost 20 000 people to join us for
these three day events called get your
music heard and launch your worship
music okay
so these were live virtual events that
we ran on Facebook
it was a free event for three days day
one day two day three I usually ended up
speaking on day number three ended up
help close those people and we sold I
believe it was like 350 copies of
that
thousand dollar course so there's
another 350 000 so we're we're right at
almost a million dollars in Revenue in
just six months time like that was from
May to November May June July August
September October yeah six months in six
months time we were able to bring in a
Million Dollars around this one concept
around this one idea of songwriting and
getting people to learn how to get their
music heard and get their music out
there okay
now this is where things got even
crazier
and I'm leading you to the million
dollar month
is Rick was like What if I sold
a ten thousand dollar coaching program
for a year of mentorship with me
to all these people who ended up going
through our schools ended up signing up
for
this program
and and then what if we also took the
main School
and we marketed it for two hundred
dollars
to another group of people
and so we ended up bringing in 3 000
people into that 200 school so there's
another six hundred thousand dollars
just with Facebook ads
and then we ended up
then marketing
the ten thousand dollar program
to people
out of this okay so you gotta you gotta
track with me here
you got to go the whole cycle so we
started
doing this membership right this was
back in 2018 this was back in 2018 we
ended up selling a membership to people
for 27 a month
and that was decently profitable 40 50
000 a month
we ended up then pivoting towards
songwriters because of the AMA where we
ended up listening to the Target
customer we ended up listening to what
people actually wanted we ended up
listening to what people actually wanted
to learn from us
and they told us we want to learn
songwriting so then we made
almost a million dollars selling
training and coaching to songwriters
who wanted to learn
how to write better songs they wanted to
get mentored in this
and then we ended up
launching this brand of events that were
free on Facebook
called get your music heard and before
you think okay it's gonna take me four
years to do this honestly we could have
done this in about six months
um I have my theories as to why it took
four years to do it
um
I think it could have only taken six
months if we had actually gone step by
step by step and actually just followed
this process which is what I teach
people to do now is you can actually
just follow this process of asking your
audience what they want
and you develop offers around what they
want and you might have to Pivot away
from what you originally started with
you might have to Pivot away from
that like okay when you first launched
your first program your first Niche it's
your baby
I think that this is the biggest reason
why it took so long is because the baby
that was first launched with wasn't
really producing the results that we
wanted it to
and so you have to
not be emotionally attached to your
offers to the point that you're not
willing to Pivot your Niche where you're
not willing to expand your Niche out
even more
to the group of people that are actually
willing to spend money
and you want to start to segment out the
people that are wasting your time that
are not willing to spend money with you
and you want to focus all of your energy
towards those that actually will spend
money with you
okay
and so
we launched with that one Niche we
pulled the audience what do they want to
learn songwriting great and then from
six months in about six months we were
able to Pivot
and create songwriting training
and then how do you launch your music
and then how do you get your songs
listened to by people and then from
there
that's where the million dollar month
comes in is
what if
a segment of those people that we've
been working with for six months
and you can actually shrink this down to
about a three month cycle doesn't need
to be a six month cycle
what if a segment of them wants to
invest ten thousand dollars for an
entire year
to be personally mentored
in a group setting
on how to write better songs and get
their music heard and so from that 150
people ended up signing up for the ten
thousand dollar program
or I think it was 160 something like
that
and and then we figured out okay we can
automate this whole process and we did
it not once but twice
and and and and that my friends was the
inside of how we were able to build a
million dollar a month sales funnel
was because by listening to the Target
customer
and then creating
okay a hundred dollar training
now we have a Next Level thousand dollar
training
and now we have a next level
another thousand dollar training
and and now we might go back and we did
a 200 training
and now we have a next level ten
thousand dollar training to that whole
group of people because they had trust
established we had nurtured and
established trust with people they had
learned how to write songs but they
wanted to go to the next level and so
out of this I think it was close to
almost 20 to 30 000 people that came in
from the ads
I think how much money was spent on ads
for this
I think it ended up being no more than
about ten to twenty thousand dollars per
month you might say well I don't have
twenty thousand dollars a month to start
with start with what you got
if you start with what you got you can
get results my client Emma Dixon
spent 693 pounds on one of her offers
brought in 9 500 pounds in sales in one
month using this exact process that I'm
talking about with you right now
and so the six step framework is you
find your niche
you write your offer copy write your
offer copy is the the words that you use
on the page
the words that you use and the language
that you use that actually connects with
the Target customer so for instance just
learning about growing with God was
different than
write songs
get them heard become a famous worship
leader go on tour and have award-winning
records like that's different language
those are different words there's a
different type of a person who's going
to actually sign up for that and so when
you find your niche
that's step number one step number two
is you write your sales copy your offer
copy the actual words that are on the
page
that connect with people
you actually write those words
on the page
and then you create a landing page and
you put it up on a website
and you promote it with your social
media your email list and paid
advertising
and you get people to sign up for your
offer and then when those people sign up
for that offer
you sell them in a presentation on your
paid program this is the process that we
teach people how to do
and you ascend those people as you build
trust with them on into higher level
higher ticket training programs
and so you might initially have a free
offer it's for three days you'll sell
people on a thousand dollar or a two
thousand dollar training
and then a group of those people you'll
offer them a ten thousand dollar
coaching package I did this this month
in our business we brought in a hundred
and sixty thousand dollars in sales
and you can do the same thing as well
and as you get
now why did my business only bring 160
000 not a million this month right
because we're still developing our offer
copy we're still honing in that language
of what is specifically going to get
people to actually sign up with us
and so it's all about
not being emotionally attached to your
baby that you first launched with being
willing to Pivot your Niche towards
what's most profitable for you and then
creating an Ascension ladder of offers
that take your most committed people
that are willing to make an investment
right because that's actually the most
important part who is willing to make an
investment
not who needs the most help
who needs the most help is usually going
to not spend much money with you and
that's important to understand who is
actually willing to make the investment
you build all of your offers around
those people specifically
and then you just sell to them
their hopes and dreams
so the hopes and dreams of people who
might sign up for a worship
songwriting get your songs heard become
a famous worship leader packages
literally selling that hope and dream of
winning an award
that was one of the taglines we use
we'll walk you all the way to the awards
show for ten thousand dollars well we'll
go from zero to the award show for ten
thousand dollars and that language
resonated with the right people who are
willing to make an investment and so
this is why I stress so often the
language that you use is what determines
who you're going to attract with your
offers with your ads with your campaigns
and when you're building your funnel
your your goal is to constantly iterate
and get feedback from people you want to
listen to your target audience as to
what they want the most
and then give them that and it might not
be the thing that you want to give them
initially
but what are they willing to throw money
at you for
that is what you want to build your
offer around
and that is what created a million
dollar funnel with my client Rick Pino
and so
you and you could do this and duplicate
this across
multiple Industries my mom did the same
thing with stocks
she's got a 12 000 program she did I
think
she had close to 80 people signed up for
a 12K program
and she has 3 000 people in her 177 a
month program
it's the same exact model no matter what
industry you're in
anybody can do this any coach any course
creator can do this it's not rocket
science it's actually way simpler than
you guys think and using jasper.i the
artificial intelligence sales
copywriting software that we use is the
number one ticket to be able to do this
so I hope this encourages you again
get on the waiting list for my client
growth accelerator the group coaching
program where I help you and work with
you and hold your hand through the
process of getting more clients in your
business
I can't wait to talk with you I can't
wait to see you in there grow your life
everybody and we'll talk soon have a
good one